AKASH **SARKAR**

ANDROID DEVELOPER





+91 7838902089



akash.sarkar188@gmail.com



New Delhi



linkedin.com/in/akashsarkar188

SKILLS

- Core Java
- Android App Development
- Git, SQL, Postman
- Firebase, REST APIs
- · Adobe XD, Figma

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY - CSE

Delhi Technical Campus

2016 - 2020

SENIOR SECONDARY - SCIENCE

Kendriya Vidyalaya Janakpuri

2015 - 2016

SECONDARY

Kendriya Vidyalaya Janakpuri

2013 - 2014

PROJECTS

ASPIRE BUDGETING

aspirebudgetmobile.app/

CORONA TRACKER

github.com/PsychoDevs69/CoronaTracker

PROFILE

A dedicated developer with a product mindset and a team player experienced in solving problems, making efficient and scalable apps, improving performance and driving product growth. Currently having 3+ years of experience; Exploring new challenges!

EXPERIENCE

ANDROID DEVELOPER

SalaryBox (1M+ App downloads)

May 2021 - Present

- Owned complete Android app and lead the development.
- Implemented live tracking, payment gateway, geofencing, card scanner, realtime communication, graphic editor.
- Researched, implemented and tested successful growth hacks!
- Improved app crash free users, performance, code structure.

ANDROID DEVELOPER

Canticle Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

Sept 2020 - April 2021

- Developed new applications as per business requirements.
- Implemented face recognition, barcode Scanners, offline attendance.
- Refactored the existing codebase to clean code.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Achiredo Technologies LLP

Jan 2020 - Sept 2020

- Developed new features in existing application.
- Created UI designs for web and mobile application.

ANDROID DEVELOPER

Ghar Pe Shiksha

Jun 2019 - Dec 2019

- Developed both user facing application.
- Implemented Chatbot.